fortytwo.sg 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy | Online Shopping | FortyTwo | Furniture & Home Décor | FortyTwo

#### FortyTwo's Commitment To Your Privacy

Your privacy is very important to us. Hence we're providing this Statement to explain our online information collection and usage practices, as well as to inform you on the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on the Website.

#### Scope

This Privacy Policy Statement covers all aspects of the FortyTwo Website (www.fortytwo.sg). The information ("Information") referred to in this Statement is the personal information any individual furnishes to FortyTwo through the Website.

#### Information Types Collected

FortyTwo collects two different types of information off this Website: Website Visitor Information through and Personal Identity Information voluntarily provided to FortyTwo by FortyTwo customers and Website visitors.

#### Website Visitor Information

FortyTwo routinely collects Information on Website activity. This includes website traffic data (eg. the number of people who visit the Website, the individual pages they view, how long they stay on each page, etc).

All Website Visitor Information is collected on an anonymous and aggregated basis, through web server logs for the purpose of generating statistics. No personal identifiable information is collected.

We use this information to monitor the activity on the website and improve on the efficiency and effectiveness of the Website.

#### Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information is only collected on certain pages of the FortyTwo Website. This Information is collected when you fill in our online order/contact forms, join our forums, or take part voluntarily in our online surveys.

The Personally Identifiable Information you submit to us can include your name, contact numbers, mailing and billing addresses, e-mail address, model name and number of purchased product and dates of purchase, as well as your questions and comments.

This information is only collected from you when you use portions of the site which require us to register these details. All information is provided to us voluntarily by you. Most of the site is still accessible and usable without any need for the submission of Personally Identifiable Information.

#### How FortyTwo Uses Your Information

This Information, which you voluntarily provide to us, is used purely to perform the service which you have requested.

Your Information may be shared among our employees, delivery agents or distributors to provide the products and/or services you have requested. FortyTwo may also occasionally use this Information to send you promotional messages, newsletters and/or conduct surveys and studies to improve our products and services to you. External parties may be engaged to perform these surveys and studies and may be given your Information on a private and confidential basis to facilitate these surveys and studies.

The FortyTwo Website may contain hyperlinks to other Internet websites. This Privacy Policy statement applies only to this Website and this website is not bound by the privacy policies of other websites, nor are their websites bound by our Privacy Policy. As these other websites have their own privacy practices from the ones described here, FortyTwo advises you to read the privacy statements of other websites you visit.

FortyTwo will release Information when we determine that such release is required to comply with laws and/or Website regulations, or to protect the rights, property, and/or safety of FortyTwo, FortyTwo Website users or others.

FortyTwo does not sell your Personally Identifiable Information. You may unsubscribe from any of our promotional messaging services whenever you wish.

#### FortyTwo's Right To Amend Privacy Policy

FortyTwo reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy Statement at its own discretion and all changes in Policy are effective upon publishing. We advise you to check this Privacy Policy frequently for any updates.

#### Contact FortyTwo

Should you have any queries regarding this Statement, please contact FortyTwo at:  
Our Office Address:

 **5 Toh Guan Road East, #05-01**  
**Singapore 608831**  
E-mail: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#57342417313825232e232038792430)  
Telephone: [6777 7667](callto:cs@fortytwo.sg)
